https://chicagolegalnet.com/privacy-policy/

Quick Contact Form
(Within hours)
Daytime Phone/Cell:*
Evening Phone:
Best Time To Call:
Message:*
What is the color of a stop sign?
Cases We Handle
United Airlines EmployeesFirefighters, Paramedics, Police Officers and Certain Other Public EmployeesUnion MembersWorkers' CompensationCarpal Tunnel SyndromeAll Types of Injury CasesRetaliatory DischargeSexual HarassmentEmployment DiscriminationStatutes of LimitationsFair Labor Standards Act (FLSA)Do I Need an Attorney?Overtime Wage ClaimsFamily Medical Leave ActSocial SecurityWorking WomenBack InjuriesChicago Transit Authority (CTA) And Workers CompensationFord Motor Company And Illinois Workers' Compensation
YOU HAVE A LEGAL RIGHT
To Get a Second Opinion »
WHAT IS MY CLAIM WORTH?
Get a Case Evaluation »
WORKERS’ COMP FAQ’s »
PERSONAL INJURY FAQ’s »
Recent Settlements
Firefighter Injury
$400,000 Workers' Comp settlement
More results
Painter Accident
$1,785,000 Settlement for fall
More results
Illinois Police & Firefighters
Union Members
Airlines Employees
Privacy Policy
The Firm is committed to the protection of your privacy, and will treat all of the information you provide through the Firm Web site, including your registration information, with the utmost respect. The Firm works diligently to ensure that it has taken all appropriate administrative and technical measures to prevent the unauthorized or unlawful use of your personally identifiable information, and to prevent any accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, such information. The Firm will not sell or disclose personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third parties except in accordance with this “Privacy Policy”.
Collection of Information.
1. The Firm Web site collects certain information about visitors, even when they are not logged in. The Firm may record your IP address, the URLs of the Web sites and pages you visit (before, during and after your visit to the Firm Web site), the times and dates of such visits, information about the computer hardware and software you use and other information that may be available. Also, The Firm may place “cookies” on your computer to recognize you on return visits to enable The Firm to enhance your browsing experience, as well as to collect additional information about you. You may adjust your browser settings or use other means to prevent cookies from being placed on your computer, but doing so may result in reduced functionality and a less personalized browsing experience.
2. The Firm may ask you to provide certain additional information about yourself, including your name, contact information, the organization you come from and certain other information that The Firm may use to identify you. If you choose not to provide such information, you may not be permitted to access certain Firm Web site features, content or services.
Use of Information.
1. The Firm uses the information that it collects about you to improve your browsing experience by personalizing The Firm Web sites to your interest, and also to help The Firm select content and services that you may find interesting and useful. Information about the content you visit and services you use may be used alone or in conjunction with information collected from other users to help The Firm tailor The Firm Web site and its other products and services to better suit the needs and interests of you and other users.
2. Information that you provide may also be used as part of The Firm’s effort to keep you informed about events, and selected products and services that may be of interest to you. In some cases, The Firm may contact you with information from carefully selected third parties, but The Firm will not provide information to third parties for such purposes. In other cases, your information might be shared with a third party pursuant to a process that contemplates such sharing but which you knowingly initiate.
3. The Firm reserves the right to disclose any information that it obtains through the Firm Web site to appropriate governmental or regulatory authorities, if required by law or any governmental agency.
Transfers of Information.
From time to time, The Firm may disclose information about you to carefully selected service providers that The Firm may engage to host Firm Web site or to provide other services. The Firm will require all such service providers to use the information solely to provide the specified services, and otherwise to conform to the requirements of this Privacy Policy. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, The Firm will not provide your information to third parties for any other purpose, including marketing.
Additional Services.
From time to time, The Firm may offer additional services through the Firm Web site. In some cases additional services may be subject to alternative terms of use (as identified by The Firm), and your use of any such services will constitute your acceptance of such alternative terms of use. Unless otherwise stated, such alternative terms of use shall apply to supplement this Agreement and in the context of any conflicting terms, this Agreement shall govern with respect to The Firm Web sites, content and services, excepting only those services which are expressly covered, and then only to the extent so expressly covered, by such alternative terms.
Information Sent by Way of the Web site is Not Secure
Any information sent to the firm by Internet e-mail or through the Web site is not secure and is done so on a non-confidential basis. Any information you send the Firm over the Internet, either through the Firm’s Web site or via email is done at your own risk.
Sending Information Does Not Form an Attorney – Client Relationship
Transmission of information from this Web site does not create an attorney-client relationship between you and the firm, nor is it intended to do so. The transmission of the Web site, in part or in whole, and/or any communication with us via Internet e-mail through this site does not constitute or create an attorney-client relationship between us and any recipients.
Home
About Us
Attorneys
News & Info
Client Testimonials
Blog
Videos
Contact Us
Our Locations
DONALD W. FOHRMAN &
ASSOCIATES, LTD
101 W. Grand Avenue, Suite 500
Chicago,
Illinois
60654
Toll Free: 800-437-2571
Local:312-661-0450
Get Map
| Driving Directions
NORTHBROOK, IL
Toll Free: 800-437-2571
local: 312-661-0450
© 2020 by Donald W. Fohrman & Associates, LTD.
All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy | Disclaimer | Site Map
Serving Workers Comp & Personal Injury clients throughout Illinois Chicago (Cook County), Oakbrook Terrace (DuPage County), Bannockburn (Lake County), Joliet (Will County), Springfield (Sangamon County), Rockford (Winnebago County), Bloomington - Normal (McLean County), Aurora (Kane County), Crystal Lake (McHenry County), DeKalb (Dekalb County), Champaign (Champaign County)
Lawfirm Websites by Market JD
